gamevilusa.com 2019-05-11

# GAMEVIL

View Previous Terms

PRIVACY POLICY

Table of Contents

  1. 1\. Introduction
  2. 2\. Who We Are
  3. 3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It
  4. 4\. Sharing of Your Information
  5. 5\. Retaining and Deleting Personal Data
  6. 6\. Transfer of Personal Data to Third Country
  7. 7\. Security of Your Information
  8. 8\. Our Policy Concerning Children
  9. 9\. Your Privacy Rights
  10. 10\. Change/Update to Privacy Policy
  11. 11\. Links 
  12. 12\. Data Protection Officer and Representative
  13. 13\. Questions

  1. _1\. Introduction_

We take privacy seriously, and we are committed to protecting personal data of our users (“you” or “User”).  We provide this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to help you understand how we collect, store, use, manage, share, and disclose your personal data you provide or we collect.  This Privacy Policy applies where we are acting as a data controller with respect to your personal data and is limited to data collected or received by us through your use of our Service.  By using our products and services, and agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

_Back to top_

  1. _2\. Who We Are_

GAMEVIL Inc. and/or its affiliates (“GAMEVIL”), jointly with Gamevil Com2uS Platform Inc. (“GCP” and collectively with GAMEVIL, “we” or “us”) provide GAMEVIL’s mobile games (“GAMEVIL Games” or “Games”) and related services, including, without limitation, online communities for GAMEVIL Games or social network services offered by GCP via the HIVE Platform or GAMEVIL/GCP branded websites (collectively, our “Service(s)”). 

_Back to top_

  1. _3\. Information We Collect and How We Use It_
  2.  
  3. 3.1 HIVE Account users

_Device Information_

To provide you with an access to any of GAMEVIL Games and for your use of our Services pursuant to our Terms of Service, we must at least collect and process from all of you  _your device information including MAC Address, IP Address and unique mobile device ID_  (collectively, “Device Information”).  We collect and process your Device Information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  We use your Device Information to discharge our contractual obligations to you as a User of our Services.

With your Device Information, we will:

  * \- provide access to the GAMEVIL Games and any of our Services;
  * \- create your game account and manage the account information;
  * \- inform you of (a) existing products, new products, services, features, promotions, enhancements and updates regarding our Service and (b) updates to the Policy;
  * \- fulfill your request and/or order for GAMEVIL Games and our obligations under the Policy;
  * \- monitor the technical functioning of the Service; and
  * \- trouble-shoot errors or issues with any of the Service.

_Game Data_

Our Service will also record  _game play information including, without limitation, your activities within the GAMEVIL Games, high scores or game session duration_ , for the continuation of your game play.  Any time you access the Service, we also collect  _aggregate information, including, without limitation, internet protocol addresses, your device’s operating system, browser type and browser language_.  We use the game play information and aggregate information to provide adequate services within the Services, better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Services.  We collect and process your game play information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.

_Usage Data through Automated Means_

When you access and/or use any of our Services, we may also collect your  _usage statistics_  about your interactions with our Services.  Such usage data is collected through the use of server log files and/or automated means.  We and our marketing partners and analytics service providers use technologies may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons, clear GIFs on certain our Services, Games, advertising and web pages to analyze your use of our Services, games, advertising and web pages, to customize, improve the same, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to promote trust and safety. We collect and process your usage data because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser or device permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages.  Please note that certain features of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages will not be available once cookies are declined.

_HIVE Account Registration Information_

In addition to your Device Information, when you create a HIVE Account and use the HIVE related Services, we collect the following information which must be processed in order for us to provide you with our applicable HIVE related Services pursuant to our Terms of Service:

  * \- email address and password; and
  * \- User ID and nickname.

(Collectively with email address, password, and nickname, the “HIVE Account Registration Information”)

We collect and process the HIVE Account Registration Information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  We use your HIVE Account Registration Information to discharge our contractual obligations to you as a User of our Services.

With your HIVE Account Registration Information, we will:

  * \- provide customer support and respond to User inquiries;
  * - fulfill your request and/or order for GAMEVIL Games and our obligations under the Policy;
  * - enable User-to-User communication and interaction;
  * - provide customer support and respond to user inquiries;
  * - solicit your input and feedback to improve User experience;
  * - monitor the technical functioning of the Service;
  * - develop new and/or improved games, products, services or offerings; and
  * - trouble-shoot errors or issues with any of the Service.

Please keep in mind that your profile photo, country, gender or other profile information may be publicly viewable by other HIVE users depending upon your privacy setting.  You may control the visibility of most of such profile information you share with other HIVE users at any time. 

_Additional Information_

Furthermore, upon your explicit consent, we may also collect and process below information to provide enhanced game services and promotional/marketing information regarding GAMEVIL Games via push notification and/or e-mail newsletters:

  * - for the purpose of marketing, your country, phone number, email address, and birthday;
  * - for the purpose of providing you with social networking services within the Services, your profile photo, country, gender, and contact list; and
  * - for the purpose of providing you with HIVE optional services (i.e. find your ID/password or other information to identify user/account), your birthday and secondary email address.

_(1) Contact Information for  _ _Friends Matching Service_

If you, as an Android phone user, log-in to the HIVE Platform, we may, upon your request, periodically access your  _contact list and/or address book_  on your mobile device in order to help you find any friends who may also have a HIVE Account.  We will use such contact information solely for such friends-matching service, and we will not store such information after fulfilling this purpose.  If you are an iOS user, we will not access your contact list and/or address book on your mobile device unless your identity is verified in a reasonable way.

_(2) Public Posting_

Some of GAMEVIL Games and/or the HIVE Platform may allow you to interact with other users and/or post, share, communicate with, or otherwise transmit content publicly, such as by participating in player forums, message boards, news feeds, status updates, sending messages or invitations to other users, chatting with other users, and/or posting photo (collectively, “Public Postings”).  We may collect and store archives of such Public Postings on our servers, and all Public Postings are subject to this Privacy Policy.

_(3) Telephone Number_

When you access and/or use the Service, we may collect  _your telephone number_  through automated means if you are an Android phone user, as a part of device information (if you are an iOS user, we will not collect your telephone number unless your identity is verified in a reasonable way).

  1. 3.2 Social Networking Service (“SNS”) Account

_Device Information_

To provide you with an access to any of GAMEVIL Games and for your use of our Services pursuant to our Terms of Service, we must at least collect and process from all of you  _your device information including MAC Address, IP Address and unique mobile device ID_  (collectively, “Device Information”).  We collect and process your Device Information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  We use your Device Information to discharge our contractual obligations to you as a User of our Services.

With your Device Information, we will:

  * - provide access to the GAMEVIL Games and any of our Services;
  * - create your game account and manage the account information;
  * - inform you of (a) existing products, new products, services, features, promotions, enhancements and updates regarding our Service and (b) updates to the Policy;
  * - fulfill your request and/or order for GAMEVIL Games and our obligations under the Policy;
  * - monitor the technical functioning of the Service; and
  * - trouble-shoot errors or issues with any of the Service.

_Game Data_

Our Service will also record  _game play information including, without limitation, your activities within the GAMEVIL Games, high scores or game session duration_ , for the continuation of your game play.  Any time you access the Service, we also collect  _aggregate information, including, without limitation, internet protocol addresses, your device’s operating system, browser type and browser language_.  We use the game play information and aggregate information to provide adequate services within the Services, better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Services.  We collect and process your game play information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.

_Usage Data through Automated Means_

When you access and/or use any of our Services, we may also collect your  _usage statistics_  about your interactions with our Services.  Such usage data is collected through the use of server log files and/or automated means.  We and our marketing partners and analytics service providers use technologies may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons, clear GIFs on certain our Services, Games, advertising and web pages to analyze your use of our Services, games, advertising and web pages, to customize, improve the same, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to promote trust and safety. We collect and process your usage data because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser or device permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages.  Please note that certain features of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages will not be available once cookies are declined.

_SNS Information_

When you use or access GAMEVIL Games using a third party SNS, such as Facebook, Apple Play Center or Google +, you allow us to access and/or collect certain information from your SNS profile/account as permitted by the terms of the SNS Platform and your privacy settings thereon.  To provide SNS Account users the Service and necessary customer support, we, in addition to your Device Information, collect your unique SNS identifier and your SNS profile photo (collectively, the “SNS Information”).  We collect and process your SNS Information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  We use your SNS Information to discharge our contractual obligations to you as a User of our Services.

With your SNS Information, we will:

  * - provide access to the GAMEVIL Games and any of our Services;

  * - create your game account and manage the account information;

  * - inform you of (a) existing products, new products, services, features, promotions, enhancements and updates regarding our Service and (b) updates to the Policy;

  * - provide customer support and respond to User inquiries;

  * - fulfill your request and/or order for GAMEVIL Games and our obligations under the Policy; and

  * - enable User-to-User communication and interaction

If you do not wish your SNS to provide us your personal data, you may disconnect the SNS login in the setting within the Services or change the privacy setting on your SNS.  Your deliberate disconnection of the SNS login may limit certain features of our Services.

_Additional Information_

Furthermore, upon your explicit consent, we may also collect and process below information to provide enhanced game services and promotional/marketing information regarding GAMEVIL Games via push notification and/or e-mail newsletters:

  * \- for the purpose of marketing, your country, phone number, email address, and birthday;

  * \- for the purpose of providing you with social networking services within the Services, your profile photo, country, gender, and contact list; and

  * \- for the purpose of providing you with HIVE optional services (i.e. find your ID/password or other information to identify user/account), your birthday and secondary email address.

_(1) Contact Information for  _ _Friends Matching Service_

If you, as an Android phone user, log-in to the HIVE Platform, we may, upon your request, periodically access your  _contact list and/or address book_  on your mobile device in order to help you find any friends who may also have a HIVE Account.  We will use such contact information solely for such friends-matching service, and we will not store such information after fulfilling this purpose.  If you are an iOS user, we will not access your contact list and/or address book on your mobile device unless your identity is verified in a reasonable way.

_(2) Public Posting_

Some of GAMEVIL Games and/or the HIVE Platform may allow you to interact with other users and/or post, share, communicate with, or otherwise transmit content publicly, such as by participating in player forums, message boards, news feeds, status updates, sending messages or invitations to other users, chatting with other users, and/or posting photo (collectively, “Public Postings”).  We may collect and store archives of such Public Postings on our servers, and all Public Postings are subject to this Privacy Policy.

_(3) Telephone Number_

When you access and/or use the Service, we may collect  _your telephone number_  through automated means if you are an Android phone user, as a part of device information (if you are an iOS user, we will not collect your telephone number unless your identity is verified in a reasonable way).

  1. 3.3 Users without Any Account

Users can access any of GAMEVIL Games without a HIVE or SNS Account.  These guest users (“Guest Users”) can enjoy GAMEVIL Games but may have limited access to online communities or social network services, customer support and other exclusive services rendered to HIVE or SNS Account users.

To provide you as a Guest User necessary access to GAMEVIL Games and for your use of GAMEVIL Games pursuant to the Terms of Service concluded between you and us, we collect and process below information.

_Device Information_

To provide you with an access to any of GAMEVIL Games and for your use of our Services pursuant to our Terms of Service, we must at least collect and process from all of you  _your device information including MAC Address, IP Address and unique mobile device ID_  (collectively, “Device Information”).  We collect and process your Device Information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  We use your Device Information to discharge our contractual obligations to you as a User of our Services.

With your Device Information, we will:

  * - provide access to the GAMEVIL Games and any of our Services;
  * - create your game account and manage the account information;
  * - inform you of (a) existing products, new products, services, features, promotions, enhancements and updates regarding our Service and (b) updates to the Policy;
  * - fulfill your request and/or order for GAMEVIL Games and our obligations under the Policy;
  * - monitor the technical functioning of the Service; and
  * - trouble-shoot errors or issues with any of the Service.

_Game Data_

Our Service will also record  _game play information including, without limitation, your activities within the GAMEVIL Games, high scores or game session duration_ , for the continuation of your game play.  Any time you access the Service, we also collect  _aggregate information, including, without limitation, internet protocol addresses, your device’s operating system, browser type and browser language_. We use the game play information and aggregate information to provide adequate services within the Services, better tailor the Service to your interests, to provide you more efficient customer support, and to overall enhance the Services.  We collect and process your game play information because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.

_Usage Data through Automated Means_

When you access and/or use any of our Services, we may also collect your  _usage statistics_  about your interactions with our Services.  Such usage data is collected through the use of server log files and/or automated means.  We and our marketing partners and analytics service providers use technologies may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons, clear GIFs on certain our Services, Games, advertising and web pages to analyze your use of our Services, games, advertising and web pages, to customize, improve the same, to measure promotional effectiveness, and to promote trust and safety. We collect and process your usage data because we have a legitimate business interest in providing the Services to you that do not override your interests, rights and freedoms to protect information about you.  You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser or device permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages.  Please note that certain features of our Services, Games, advertising and web pages will not be available once cookies are declined.

_Additional Information_

Furthermore, upon your explicit consent, we may also collect and process the Device Information to provide enhanced game services and promotional/marketing information regarding GAMEVIL Games, including sending you push notification.

_Telephone Number_

When you access and/or use the Service, we may collect  _your telephone number_  through automated means if you are an Android phone user, as a part of device information (if you are an iOS user, we will not collect your telephone number unless your identity is verified in a reasonable way).

_Back to top_

  1. _4\. Sharing of Your Information_

We do not share your personal data with third parties except as explicitly approved by you or except in the following circumstances:

a. Third Party Service Providers. We may provide your information to third party companies (the “Third Party Service Providers”) that perform services on our behalf, including, without limitation, operation of the HIVE platform, data analysis, marketing services, promotional events, email campaigns, hosting services, and customer service or support.  The Third Party Service Providers may access your personal data, but are required to use it solely as directed by us for performing requested services.  We will ask for your consent before we share your data with the Third Party Service Providers.

b. Business Partners. In conjunction with the running of GAMEVIL Games via the HIVE Platform, we are partnering with Com2us Corporation and its affiliates (collectively, the “Business Partners”) in order to: 

  * - assist us in providing maintenance services of the HIVE Platform and enhancing user convenience of the HIVE Platform;
  * - enable you to log-in and use the HIVE Platform when you are playing the Business Partners’ games without creating further account;
  * - enable you to receive from the Business Partners any information, newsletter or notification regarding Business Partners’ games provided via the HIVE Platform; and
  * - enable participation in any promotional event or campaign of such games arranged by the Business Partners.

We may share with our Business Partners the information you provide about yourself, such as (i) your HIVE Account Registration information, (ii) your profile information, (iii) your telephone number, (iv) any technical and usage information we collect, and/or (v) game play information, to the extent that such disclosure may serve the above-mentioned purposes and/or facilitate your use of the HIVE Platform service. We will take commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that the Business Partners use your information shared by us in compliance with any applicable laws or regulations and solely for the above-mentioned purposes.  We will ask for your consent before we share your personal data with the Business Partners.

If you wish to no longer have your personal data used by the Business Partners for their marketing purposes, please contact us at privacy@gamevil.com and we will facilitate your request to Business Partners.

c. Advertising of Third Party Products/Services. We will not actively share personal data with third party advertisers (the “Advertisers”) for their direct marketing purposes unless we obtain your consent.  We may share (i) aggregated information (information about you and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you); (ii) anonymous information; and (iii) certain technical information (including IP Addresses, MAC Addresses for mobile devices and mobile device IDs) to develop and deliver targeted advertising in the Advertiser’s website or application.  We may also allow the Advertisers to collect these and similar types of information within the Service and they may share it with us and/or use it for advertising.  The Advertisers may collect this information through the use of a variety of tracking technologies, including without limitation, browser cookies and web beacons.  The information collected may be used to offer you targeted ad-selection and delivery in order to personalize your User experience by ensuring that advertisements for products and services you see will appeal to you, a practice known as behavioral advertising, and to undertake web analytics (i.e. to analyze traffic and other end user activity to improve your experience).  We will ask for your consent before we share your personal data with the Advertisers.

If you wish to no longer have your personal data used by the Advertisers for their marketing purposes, please contact us at privacy@gamevil.com and we will facilitate your request to the Advertisers.

d. Offer Walls. GAMEVIL Games or their purchase pages may display an “offer wall” that may be hosted by a third party offer wall provider.  The offer wall allows the Advertisers to provide virtual currency to users in exchange for interacting with an advertisement or for completing a marketing offer that may include signing up for an account with one of the Advertisers.  These offers are not controlled by or made by us.  These offers may be displayed to you based on certain technical information, such as your geographic area or anonymous demographic information. After clicking on one of these advertisements, you will no longer be on a site hosted by us.  To properly credit User accounts and to prevent fraud, a unique identifier will be shared with the offer wall provider.  This identifier is used to ensure proper crediting of your account, prevent fraud or duplicate offers and to resolve any customer service inquiries that may arise.  We will ask for your consent before we share your personal data with the Advertisers.

e. Safety, Security and Compliance with Law. We may disclose your information to certain third parties if we reasonably believe that: 

  * - We are required to disclose the information in response to legal process (e.g., a court order, search warrant or subpoena); 
  * - We are required to satisfy any applicable laws, regulations, or administrative orders;
  * - There is an emergency that poses a threat to the safety condition of you, another person, or general public; and
  * - Such disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or property of GAMEVIL or GCP.

f. Sale or Merger. In the event that GAMEVIL or GCP undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or the substantial portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information you have provided, including personal data, to the successor organization in such transition if permitted by and done in accordance with any applicable law.  If material changes to our privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition, we will notify you the business transition prior to transferring your personal data.

_Back to top_

  1. _5\. Retaining and Deleting Personal Data_

We retain your information only for the period of time as necessary to achieve the particular purpose for which the information was processed.  Typically, we retain your information for 1 month after deregistration of your HIVE Account or for the duration described in the table below:

Information Retained

| 

Retention Period  
  
---|---  
  
Records of an agreement or cancellation of subscription

Records of payment

| 

5 years  
  
Records of customer complaint or dispute resolution

| 

3 years  
  
Computer communication or internet log-in records of computer communication or facts about an internet user’s utilization of telecommunication service

| 

3 months  
  
Tax and accounting records

| 

5 years  
  
Records of electronic financial transaction

| 

5 years  
  
Records of misuse by users of game services

| 

1 year  
  
Notwithstanding, we may retain your information insofar as such information will be processed solely for archiving purpose in the compliance with our legal obligation, public interest, scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes, subject to appropriate safeguards, in accordance with the data protection laws, for your rights and freedoms.  Note that in some circumstances, you have the right to request us to delete the information.  The appropriate safeguards shall ensure that technical and organizational measures are in place to ensure respect for the principle of data minimization.

_Back to top_

  1. _6\. Transfer of Personal Data to Third Country_

Your personal data may be transferred globally, either within or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including to a country or territory that may not have equivalent data protection standards.  In all cases, appropriate security measures for the protection of personal data will be applied in those countries or territories, in accordance with applicable data protection laws.  For example, we will obtain your explicit consent when your personal data is transferred to South Korea, which is currently under review of the European Commission adequacy decision.

_Back to top_

  1. _7\. Security of Your Information_

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect against unauthorized access to, or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of, sensitive data that you share and we collect and store.  Despite our efforts to enhance a security level of the Service, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur.  We strongly encourage you not to share your account password with any third parties for any reasons.  Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us personal data through these mediums.  If you have questions regarding the security measures of the Service, please contact us at privacy@gamevil.com.

_Back to top_

  1. _8\. Our Policy Concerning Children_

Children under the age of 16 can only use our game services with a valid consent from their legal representative (e.g. parents).  We make reasonable efforts to verify if consent from or any kind of contract concluded with such children is valid by offering users age verification methods and by obtaining clear consent from children’s legal representatives. If we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal data from such children, we will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records. If children under 16 or their legal representative ask us to cease processing or profiling of the child’s personal data for the purposes of direct marketing, we will immediately do so.

_Back to top_

  1. _9\. Your Privacy Rights_
  2.  
  3. 9.1 Right to Access

You are entitled to confirmation as to whether or not we process your personal data and, where we do, access to the personal data, together with certain additional information.  That additional information includes details of the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned and the recipients of the personal data.  Provided, the rights and freedoms of others are not affected, we will supply to you a copy of your personal data. You can access your personal data by logging into your HIVE Account or contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

To manage the information we receive about you from an SNS, you should change your privacy settings on the SNS in accordance with any applicable policy of the SNS. 

  1. 9.2 Right to Rectification

You are entitled to have any inaccurate personal data about you rectified and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed.

You may change or update the profile information by logging into your HIVE Account or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.3 Right to Erasure

In some circumstances you are entitled to the erasure of your personal data without undue delay.  Those circumstances include: (i) the personal data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected or otherwise processed; (ii) you withdraw consent to consent-based processing; (iii) you object to the processing under certain rules of applicable data protection law; the processing is for direct marketing purposes; and (iv) the personal data have been unlawfully processed.  However, there are exclusions of the right to erasure.  The general exclusions include where processing is necessary: (a) for exercising the right of freedom of expression and information; (b) for compliance with a legal obligation; or (c) for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

If you choose to terminate or delete your HIVE Account, we will immediately delete your HIVE Account information.  Even after your Account is terminated or deleted, some or all of your information may still remain visible to others, including but not limited to any information that has been incorporated into any User contents or copied, stored or disseminated by you or other users.

You may request erasure of your information by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.4 Right to Restrict Processing

In some circumstances you are entitled to restrict the processing of your personal data.  Those circumstances are: (i) you contest the accuracy of the personal data; (ii) processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure; (iii) we no longer need the personal data for the purposes of our processing, but you require personal data for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; and (iv) you have objected to processing, pending the verification of that objection.  Where processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your personal data.  However, we will only otherwise process it: (a) with your consent; (b) for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims; (c) for the protection of the rights of another natural or legal person; or (d) for reasons of important public interest.

You may request restriction of the processing of your information by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.5 Right to Object to Processing

You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, but only to the extent that the legal basis for the processing is that the processing is necessary for: the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of any official authority vested in us; or the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party. If you make such an objection, we will cease to process the personal data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the processing is for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

You may object to the processing of your information by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.6 Right to Object to Processing for Direct Marketing Purposes

You are entitled to object to our processing of your personal data for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal data for this purpose.

You may object to the processing of your information for direct marketing purposes by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.7 Right to Object to Processing for Scientific, Historical, or Statistical Purposes

You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data for scientific or historical research purposes or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out for reasons of public interest.

You may object to the processing of your information for scientific, historical or statistical purposes by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.8 Right to Data Portability

To the extent that the legal basis for our processing of your personal data is:

  * - consent; or
  * - that the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are party or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract,

and such processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive your personal data from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and the right to have your personal data transmitted to another controller.  However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.

You may request to receive your information by visiting https://withhive.com/help/inquire or by contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

  1. 9.9 Right to Complain to a Supervisory Authority

If you consider that our processing of your personal data infringes data protection laws, you are entitled to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection.

You can find more details of the supervisory authority in your country by visiting

<http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080>.

  1. 9.10 Right to Withdraw Consent

To the extent that the lawful basis for our processing of your personal data is consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time.  Withdrawal will not affect the lawfulness of processing before the withdrawal.

You may withdraw your consent at any time in the game setting or contacting us at privacy@gamevil.com.

You may also exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us at privacy@gamevil.com. 

_Back to top_

  1. _10\. Change/Update to Privacy Policy_

We may amend, at our discretion, any portion of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting or displaying the amended Privacy Policy within and/or on GAMEVIL Games, GAMEVIL branded website, or the HIVE Platform.  You will be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing to use the Service.  Except as otherwise stated, any such amendments will be automatically effective after they are initially posted.  Our policy will be regularly updated.  We will notify you of the changes where required by law to do so.  This policy was last updated on May 25th, 2018.

_Back to top_

  1. _11\. Links_

The Service may contain links to other websites. The fact that the Service links to a website or presents a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that we endorse or authorize that third party, nor is it a representation of our affiliation with that third party. We are in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these other websites to which you choose to access from the Service. It is your responsibility to read the privacy policies of these other websites when exiting the Service.

_Back to top_

  1. _12\. Data Protection Officer and Representative_

Our data protection officer can be reached at:

Name : Kirk Olaf Dettmann

Email : [privacy@gamevil.com](mailto:privacy@com2us.com)

Address : Wattstrasse 10, 13355 Berlin, Germany

Our representative can be reached at:

Name : GAMEVIL COM2US Europe GmbH

Email : [privacy@gamevil.com](mailto:privacy@gamevil.com)

Address : Wattstrasse 10, 13355 Berlin, Germany

_Back to top_

  1. _13\. Questions_

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices, please email us at privacy@gamevil.com. 

_Back to top_
